Guide to the Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records, 1934-2005 and undated RL.00090
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Vertical Files Series, 1934-2001, bulk 1986-1998, 138 boxes
  - Advertising agencies
    - Client relations (see also Advertising agencies--Evaluation; Advertising agencies--Selection), 1954-2000, 4 folders (Box VF19)
    - Compensation (see also Advertising agencies--Fee system), 1976-1999, 5 folders (Box VF19)
    - Consolidation, 1954-1999, 2 folders (Box VF19)
    - Creative artists, 1993 (Box VF20)
    - Departments/media, 1989-1997 (Box VF20)
    - Diversification, 1995-1996 (Box VF20)
    - Ethnic, 1985-1997 (Box VF20)
    - Evaluation (see also Advertising agencies--Client relations; Advertising agencies--Selection), 1974-1998, 3 folders (Box VF20)
    - Fee system, 1997-1999 (Box VF20)
    - Foreign (see also Advertising--Expenditures), 1996-1997 (Box VF20)
    - Full-service (vs. independent), 1971-1997 (Box VF20)
    - Independent services/A la carte, etc., 1995-1998 (Box VF20)
    - Interactive, 1996-1998 (Box VF20)
    - Mergers, 1995-1998 (Box VF21)
    - [Revenue: see Compensation] (Box VF21)
    - Salaries and personnel (see also Advertising--Careers), 1996-1997 (Box VF21)
    - Selection (see also Advertising agencies--Client relations; Advertising agencies--Evaluation), 1980-1999 (Box VF21)
  - [Affluent market: see Marketing--Affluent] (Box VF21)
  - African-American market (see also Marketing--Ethnic), 1962-1996, 2 folders (Box VF21)
  - [Aging: see Mature market] (Box VF21)
  - Aircraft, 1992-1997 (Box VF21)
  - Air freight, 1986-1998, 2 folders (Box VF21)
  - Airlines
    - General, 1995-1999, 3 folders (Box VF21)
    - Fares, 1997-1999 (Box VF22)
    - Frequent fliers, 1986-1998 (Box VF22)
    - Safety/Traffic, 1989-1997 (Box VF22)
    - Statistics, 1986-1996, 6 folders (Box VF22)
  - Airports, 1996-1997 (Box VF22)
  - [Alcoholic beverages: see Beer; Liquor] (Box VF22)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA), 1986-1994, Folder 1 of 2 (Box VF22)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA), 1986-1994 (continued), Folder 2 of 2 (Box VF23)
  - [American Indians: see Marketing--Ethnic] (Box VF23)
  - Amusement parks, 1995-1999 (Box VF23)
  - Apparel (see also Children's apparel/shoes)
    - General, 1994-1999, 3 folders (Box VF23)
    - Hosiery, 1988-1997 (Box VF23)
    - Intimate, 1989-1997, 2 folders (Box VF23)
    - Jeans, 1986-1999, 2 folders (Box VF23)
    - Sports, 1996-1998 (Box VF24)
  - [Appliances: see Electrical appliances] (Box VF24)
  - Armed forces, 1941-1975 (Box VF24)
  - [Asian market: see Marketing--Ethnic] (Box VF24)
  - [Audio: see Recording and phonograph industry] (Box VF24)
  - [Audio cassettes: see Recording and phonograph industry] (Box VF24)
  - Automobiles
    - General, 1971-1999, 4 folders (Box VF24)
    - Accessories, 1989-1998 (Box VF24)
    - Advertising, 1996-1999 (Box VF24)
    - Automotive aftermarket, 1994-1998 (Box VF25)
    - Compact cars, 1995 (Box VF25)
    - Electric vehicles, 1992-1998 (Box VF25)
    - Foreign cars, 1990-1998, 2 folders (Box VF25)
    - Luxury, 1996-1999 (Box VF25)
    - Rental, 1977-1999, 2 folders (Box VF25)
    - Sales/Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box VF25)
    - Sport Utility Vehicles (SUVs), 1996-1999 (Box VF25)
    - Used cars, 1996-1997 (Box VF25)
  - Awards, Advertising
    - General, 1983-1998, Folders 1-2 of 6 (Box VF25)
    - General, 1983-1998 (continued), Folders 3-6 of 6 (Box VF26)
    - Addy's, 1987-1997, 4 folders (Box VF26)
    - Cannes, 1996-1998 (Box VF27)
  - Babies, 1958-1997 (Box VF27)
  - Baby boom (see also Lifestyles), 1991-1998, 4 folders (Box VF27)
  - Baby market, 1994-1999 (Box VF27)
  - Baggage/Handbags/Luggage, 1994-1997 (Box VF27)
  - Banking/Banks
    - General, 1991-1999, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box VF27)
    - General, 1991-1999 (continued), Folders 3-5 of 5 (Box VF28)
    - Advertising, 1996-2000 (Box VF28)
    - Automation and services, 1996-2000 (Box VF28)
    - Credit cards, 1989-2000, 5 folders (Box VF28)
    - Debit cards, 1996-1997 (Box VF29)
    - Smart cards, 1996-1998 (Box VF29)
  - [Barter arrangements: see Television] (Box VF29)
  - [Bathroom tissue: see Paper products--Facial and bathroom tissue] (Box VF29)
  - Batteries, 1996-1998 (Box VF29)
  - Beer
    - General, 1994-1998, 3 folders (Box VF29)
    - Advertising, 1970-1999, 3 folders (Box VF29)
    - History and manufacturers, 1948-1965 (Box VF29)
    - Imported, 1989-1998 (Box VF29)
    - Low calorie or Lite, 1977-1993 (Box VF29)
    - Pricing, 1980s-1993 (Box VF29)
    - Regional and microbreweries, 1992-1998 (Box VF29)
    - Statistics, 1984-2000, 2 folders (Box VF30)
  - Beverages
    - General, 1988-2000, 5 folders (Box VF30)
    - Coffee
      - General, 1992-1999, Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box VF30)
      - General, 1992-1999 (continued), Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box VF31)
      - Decaffeinated, 1985-1995 (Box VF31)
      - Market data/consumer statistics, 1984-1996, 2 folders (Box VF31)
    - Juices, 1992-1998 (Box VF31)
    - [Liquor: see Liquor] (Box VF31)
    - [Milk: see Food--Dairy--Milk] (Box VF31)
    - New Age, 1994-1998 (Box VF31)
    - Soft Drinks
      - General, 1967-1999, 5 folders (Box VF31)
      - Caffeine-free, 0983-0984 (Box VF32)
      - [Diet: see Beverages--Soft drinks--Low calorie] (Box VF32)
      - Low calorie, 1997-1999 (Box VF32)
      - Market surveys, 1992-1999 (Box VF32)
    - Sports drinks (see also Food--Nutraceuticals), 1992-1997 (Box VF32)
    - Tea
      - General, 1934-1998 (Box VF32)
      - Ready-to-drink (RTD), 1995-1998 (Box VF32)
    - [Water: see Water--Bottled] (Box VF32)
  - Bicycles (see also Motorcycles), 1986-1997 (Box VF32)
  - Birth control (see also Drugs--Fertility; Condoms), 1987-1999, 2 folders (Box VF32)
  - [Black market: see Marketing--Ethnic] (Box VF32)
  - [Brainstorming: see Advertising--Creativity] (Box VF32)
  - Brands
    - Equity, 1991-1999, 3 folders (Box VF32)
    - Extensions, 1982-1998, 3 folders (Box VF33)
    - History, 1998 (Box VF33)
    - Image, 1985-1999, 4 folders (Box VF33)
    - Loyalty, 1989-1999, 2 folders (Box VF33)
    - Management, 1974-1999, 5 folders (Box VF34)
    - Names
      - General, 1988-1999, 5 folders (Box VF34)
      - Global, 1991-1998 (Box VF35)
      - Private label, 1992-1998, 4 folders (Box VF35)
    - Positioning (see also Product positioning), 1976-1999, 2 folders (Box VF35)
    - Relationships, 1993 (Box VF35)
    - Valuation, 1990-1999, Folder 1 of 2 (Box VF35)
    - Valuation, 1990-1999 (continued), Folder 2 of 2 (Box VF36)
  - [Breakfast: see Nutrition] (Box VF36)
  - [Bridal: see Wedding market] (Box VF36)
  - Business
    - General, 1990-1999, 6 folders (Box VF36)
    - American (Made in America), 1998 (Box VF36)
    - Conditions/Inflation, 1973-1999 (Box VF36)
    - Entrepreneurs, 1985-1997 (Box VF36)
    - Forecasts (see also Advertising--Future/Forecasts; Future trends), 1979-1999, Folder 1 of 4 (Box VF36)
    - Forecasts (see also Advertising--Future/Forecasts; Future trends), 1979-1999 (continued), Folders 2-4 of 4 (Box VF37)
    - Recession, 1974-1992 (Box VF37)
  - Cable television
    - General, 1983-1999, Folders 1-5 of 6 (Box VF37)
    - General, 1983-1999 (continued), Folders 6 of 6 (Box VF38)
    - Advertising, 1983-1999, 2 folders (Box VF38)
    - Historical, 1964-1972 (Box VF38)
    - MTV, 1989-1996 (Box VF38)
    - Pay Per View, 1989-1995 (Box VF38)
    - Television channels, 1990-1999, 2 folders (Box VF38)
  - [Camcorders: see Photography] (Box VF38)
  - [Cameras: see Photography] (Box VF38)
  - [Car accessories: see Automobile--Accessories] (Box VF38)
  - [Car rental: see Automobile--Rental] (Box VF38)
  - [Carpets: see Floor covering] (Box VF38)
  - [Cartoon characters: see Advertising--Comics] (Box VF38)
  - Case studies
    - Marketing, 1992-1998, Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box VF38)
    - Marketing, 1992-1998 (continued), Folders 2-4 of 4 (Box VF39)
    - Success stories, 1986-1999, 2 folders (Box VF39)
  - CD-ROM, 1996-1997 (Box VF39)
  - [CDs: see Recording and phonograph industry (compact disks); Financial services--Investments (certificates of deposit)] (Box VF39)
  - Celebrations and anniversaries, 1996-1998 (Box VF39)
  - [Cellular: see Telephone industry--Wireless] (Box VF39)
  - [Charities: see Philanthropy] (Box VF39)
  - [Children: see Advertising--Children; Television--Children; Youth market] (Box VF39)
  - Children's apparel/shoes, 1996-1998 (Box VF39)
  - [Cigarettes: see Tobacco--Cigarettes] (Box VF39)
  - [Cleaning products: see Household cleaners] (Box VF39)
  - [Clocks: see Watches] (Box VF39)
  - [Clothing: see Apparel] (Box VF39)
  - Co-branding, 1995-1998 (Box VF39)
  - Collectibles, 1996-1998 (Box VF40)
  - [College market: see Youth market--College] (Box VF40)
  - [Cologne: see Perfume] (Box VF40)
  - Color, 1956-1998, 3 folders (Box VF40)
  - [Comics: see Television--Comics] (Box VF40)
  - [Commercials: see Television--Commercials] (Box VF40)
  - [Common Market: see European Economic Community] (Box VF40)
  - [Compact Disks: see Recording industry] (Box VF40)
  - Computers
    - General, 1991-1998, Folders 1-3 of 5 (Box VF40)
    - General, 1991-1998 (continued), Folders 4-5 of 5 (Box VF41)
    - Advertising/Marketing/Sales promotion (see also Advertising--Technology), 1991-1998 (Box VF41)
    - Business applications, 1994-1998, 2 folders (Box VF41)
    - [CD-ROMs: see CD-ROMs] (Box VF41)
    - Education, 1985-1998 (Box VF41)
    - Foreign markets, 1996 (Box VF41)
    - Graphics/Virtual reality (see also Interactive systems), 1996-1997 (Box VF41)
    - Hardware, 1996-1998 (Box VF41)
    - Home uses, 1995-1998 (Box VF41)
    - [Internet: see Internet] (Box VF41)
    - [Laptops: see Computers--Portable/Hand-held] (Box VF41)
    - Portable/Hand-held, 1995-1998 (Box VF42)
    - Printers, 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box VF42)
    - Retail, 1996-1998 (Box VF42)
    - [Sales promotion: see Computers--Advertising] (Box VF42)
    - Software, 1984-1998, 2 folders (Box VF42)
    - Statistics and sales, 1995-1998 (Box VF42)
    - Users, 1998 (Box VF42)
    - [Virtual reality: see Computers--Graphics/Virtual reality] (Box VF42)
    - [World Wide Web: see Internet] (Box VF42)
  - Condoms (see also Birth control), 1988-1999, 3 folders (Box VF42)
  - Consumers
    - Attitudes, 1973-1999, Folder 1 of 7 (Box VF42)
    - Attitudes, 1973-1998 (continued), Folders 2-7 of 7 (Box VF43)
    - Confidence, 1993-1998 (Box VF43)
    - [Electronics: see Home electronics] (Box VF43)
    - Expenditures, 1987-1998, 2 folders (Box VF43)
    - Income, 1996-1998 (Box VF43)
    - Satisfaction, 1996-1997 (Box VF43)
    - Shopping habits (Box VF44)
      - General, 1985-1996, 6 folders (Box VF44)
      - Male/Female, 1987-1999, 2 folders (Box VF44)
  - [Contact lenses: see Eyeglasses/Hearing aids/Contact lenses] (Box VF44)
  - [Continuity programs: see Advertising--Premiums] (Box VF44)
  - [Contests: see Games] (Box VF44)
  - Copyright law, 1996 (Box VF44)
  - Corporate image (see also Advertising--Corporate; Trademarks), 1979-1999, 5 folders (Box VF45)
  - Cosmetics
    - General, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box VF45)
    - Make-up, 1996-1998 (Box VF45)
    - Skin care, 1992-1999, 4 folders (Box VF46)
    - Statistics and sales, 1996-1999 (Box VF46)
  - Cost of living, 1996-1998 (Box VF46)
  - [Countries: see Foreign markets] (Box VF46)
  - [Coupons: see Advertising--Coupons] (Box VF46)
  - [Creativity: see Advertising--Creativity] (Box VF46)
  - [Credit cards: see Banking/Banks--Credit cards] (Box VF46)
  - Crime, 1996 (Box VF46)
  - Crisis Management, 1996-1998 (Box VF46)
  - [Cross-media: see Advertising--Cross-media] (Box VF46)
  - Customer loyalty programs (see also Brands--Loyalty), 1996-1999, 2 folders (Box VF46)
  - [Customer satisfaction: see Consumer--Satisfaction] (Box VF46)
  - Death (life expectancy), 1997 (Box VF46)
  - Dental care, 1996-1998 (Box VF46)
  - Dentifrices, 1945-1999, 3 folders (Box VF46)
  - Deodorants, 1996-1999 (Box VF47)
  - Detergents, 1996-1999 (Box VF47)
  - Diapers and diaper services, 1996-1999 (Box VF47)
  - [Diet aids: see Reducing aids] (Box VF47)
  - [Diet foods: see Food--Dietetic] (Box VF47)
  - [DINKs (dual income, no kids): see Marketing] (Box VF47)
  - Direct marketing
    - General, 1995-1999, 2 folders (Box VF47)
    - Catalogs, 1994-1999, 3 folders (Box VF47)
    - [Coupons: see Marketing--Coupons] (Box VF47)
    - Direct mail, 1995-1999, 2 folders (Box VF47)
    - Statistics, 1994-1996 (Box VF47)
    - Telephone, 1988-1998 (Box VF48)
    - [Television: see Home shopping; Television--Commercials] (Box VF48)
  - [Do it yourself: see Home repair; Retail outlets and retailing] (Box VF48)
  - Drug companies, 1995-2000, 3 folders (Box VF48)
  - Drug stores and pharmacies, 1985-1999, 5 folders (Box VF48)
  - Drugs (Box VF49)
    - General, 1996-1999, 2 folders (Box VF49)
    - Abuse, 1979-1993, 2 folders (Box VF49)
    - [Acne: see Drugs--Dermatology/Acne] (Box VF49)
    - Allergy, 1996-1999 (Box VF49)
    - [Alternative: see Drugs--Homeopathic] (Box VF49)
    - [Analgesics: see Drugs--Pain relievers/analgesics] (Box VF49)
    - [Antacids: see Drugs--Indigestion] (Box VF49)
    - Antibiotics, 1996-1997 (Box VF49)
    - Anti-depressants, 1996-1997 (Box VF49)
    - [Aspirin: see Drugs--Pain relievers/analgesics] (Box VF49)
    - [Birth control: see Birth control; Condoms] (Box VF49)
    - Brand names vs. generic, 1996-1999 (Box VF49)
    - Caffeine, 1996-1999 (Box VF49)
    - Cold remedies, 1994-1999, 3 folders (Box VF49)
    - Dermatology/acne, 1996-1997 (Box VF49)
    - Diarrhea, 1996-1997 (Box VF49)
    - [Diet pills: see Reducing aids] (Box VF49)
    - [Douches: see Feminine hygiene] (Box VF49)
    - Eye preparations/drops, 1996-2000 (Box VF49)
    - Fertility, 1997-1998 (Box VF49)
    - [Generic: see Drugs--Brand name vs. generic] (Box VF49)
    - [Hay fever: see Drugs--Allergy] (Box VF49)
    - [Headaches and pain: see Drugs--Pain relievers/analgesics] (Box VF49)
    - Heart, 1997-1998 (Box VF49)
    - Homeopathic (see also Herbs), 1996-1999 (Box VF50)
    - Indigestion remedies, 1985-2000, 2 folders (Box VF50)
    - Nasal spray, 1997-1998 (Box VF50)
    - Over the Counter (OTC), 1989-1998, 5 folders (Box VF50)
    - Pain relievers/analgesics (Box VF51)
      - General, 1995-1999 (Box VF51)
      - Analysis, 1995-1999, 2 folders (Box VF51)
    - Prescription, 1991-2000, 2 folders (Box VF51)
    - Stomach upset: see Drugs--Indigestion remedies] (Box VF51)
    - Sunburn lotions and remedies, 1996-1998 (Box VF51)
    - Ulcers, 1991-1997 (Box VF51)
  - [Eating habits: see Food--Eating habits] (Box VF51)
  - [Economic indicators: see Advertising--Future/Forecasts] (Box VF51)
  - [EDLP (Everyday Low Price): see Prices; Retail] (Box VF51)
  - Education
    - General, 1990-1998, Folders 1-3 of 4 (Box VF51)
    - General, 1990-1998 (continued), Folder 4 of 4 (Box VF52)
    - Statistics, 1990-1998 (Box VF52)
  - [Elderly: see Mature market] (Box VF52)
  - Elections (see also Advertising--Political), 1990-1997, 3 folders (Box VF52)
  - Electrical appliances (see also Home electronics)
    - General, 1983-1999, 2 folders (Box VF52)
    - Microwave ovens (see also Food--Microwave), 1979-1998 (Box VF53)
    - Statistics, 1987-1996, 3 folders (Box VF53)
    - White goods, 1993-1998 (Box VF53)
  - Electronic mail, 1984-1996 (Box VF53)
  - [Electronics: see Home electronics] (Box VF53)
  - Employment, 1981-1999, Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box VF53)
  - Employment, 1981-1999 (continued), Folder 5 of 5 (Box VF54)
  - Energy (see also Gasoline and oil; Utilities), 1992-1999 (Box VF54)
  - [Energy bars: see Food--Nutraceuticals] (Box VF54)
  - Entertainment, 1993-1998, 2 folders (Box VF54)
  - Environment, 1989-1998, 3 folders (Box VF54)
  - [Ethnicity: see Marketing--Ethnic] (Box VF54)
  - European Economic Community (EEC), 1989-1998, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box VF54)
  - European Economic Community (EEC), 1989-1998 (continued), Folder 3 of 3 (Box VF55)
  - Events marketing (see also Sports--Advertising and marketing)
    - General, 1989-1998, 2 folders (Box VF55)
    - Booklets, 1986-1989 (Box VF55)
    - Sponsorship, 1991-1998, 5 folders
      - Disk 68. Auto Racing (Box VF55)
      - Disk 69. Golf (Box VF55)
      - Disk 70. Causes (Box VF55)
      - Disk 71. Arenas/auditoriums (Box VF55)
      - Disk 72. Professional sports leagues (Box VF55)
    - Trade shows, 1994-1998 (Box VF55)
  - [Every Day Low Pricing (EDLP): see Prices; Retail] (Box VF55)
  - [Exercising: see Health] (Box VF55)
  - Eyeglasses/Hearing aids/Contact lenses (see also Drugs--Eye preparations/Eye drops), 1989-1998, Folder 1 of 2 (Box VF55)
  - Eyeglasses/Hearing aids/Contact lenses (see also Drugs--Eye preparations/Eye drops), 1989-1998 (continued), Folder 2 of 2 (Box VF56)
  - [Facsimile: see Office equipment] (Box VF56)
  - Families
    - General, 1983-1999, 6 folders (Box VF56)
    - Booklets, 1982-1993, Folder 1 of 4 (Box VF56)
    - Booklets, 1982-1993 (continued), Folders 2-4 of 4 (Box VF57)
  - [Fax machines: see Office equipment] (Box VF57)
  - [FCC: see Federal Communications Commission] (Box VF57)
  - [FDA: see Food and Drug Administration (FDA)] (Box VF57)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1961-1997, 2 folders (Box VF57)
  - Feminine hygiene, 1984-1997 (Box VF57)
  - Financial services
    - General, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box VF57)
    - Booklets, 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box VF58)
    - Investments
      - General, 1996-1998, 3 folders (Box VF58)
      - Mutual funds, 1995-1999, Folders 1-3 of 5 (Box VF58)
      - Mutual funds, 1995-1999 (continued), Folders 4-5 of 5 (Box VF59)
      - Retirement planning, 1997-1998 (Box VF59)
      - Stocks and bonds, 1981-1998, 4 folders (Box VF59)
  - [Fitness: see Health] (Box VF59)
  - [Flavor: see Food--Flavor] (Box VF59)
  - [Fluorides: see Dentifrices] (Box VF59)
  - [FM Radio: see Radio--FM] (Box VF59)
  - Food
    - General, 1964-2001, Folder 1 of 5 (Box VF59)
    - General, 1964-2001 (continued), Folders 2-5 of 5 (Box VF60)
    - Advertising, 1996-2000 (Box VF60)
    - [Allergies: see Medical--Allergies] (Box VF60)
    - [Appetizers: see Food--Side dishes] (Box VF60)
    - Baby food (see also Baby market), 1996-1998 (Box VF60)
    - Bagels, 1966-1996 (Box VF60)
    - Baked, 1996-1999 (Box VF60)
    - [Beverages: see Beverages] (Box VF60)
    - Bread, 1996-1999 (Box VF60)
    - Breakfast, 1991-2000 (Box VF60)
    - [Butter: see Food--Dairy] (Box VF60)
    - [Calories: see Food--Dietetic] (Box VF60)
    - Candy
      - General, 1986-1999, Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box VF60)
      - General, 1986-1999 (continued), Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box VF61)
      - Confections, 1947-1986 (Box VF61)
      - Statistics, 1983-1999, 2 folders (Box VF61)
    - [Catsup: see Food--Condiments] (Box VF61)
    - Cereal, 1992-1999, 2 folders (Box VF61)
    - [Cheese: see Food--Dairy--Cheese] (Box VF61)
    - Chewing gum and mints, 1958-1999 (Box VF61)
    - Chocolate, 1959-1999, 2 folders (Box VF61)
    - [Coffee: see Beverages--Coffee] (Box VF61)
    - Condiments, 1987-1998, 2 folders (Box VF61)
    - Cookies and crackers, 1983-1998, 3 folders (Box VF62)
    - Dairy
      - General, 1992-1998 (Box VF62)
      - Cheese, 1994-1998 (Box VF62)
      - Ice cream
        - General, 1992-1999, 2 folders (Box VF62)
        - Pamphlets, 1979-1993, 3 folders (Box VF62)
      - Milk, 1985-1998, 3 folders (Box VF63)
      - Pamphlets, 1953-1992, 3 folders (Box VF63)
      - Statistics, 1992-1997 (Box VF63)
      - Yogurt, 1992-1998 (Box VF63)
    - Desserts, 1991-1999 (Box VF63)
    - Dietetic, 1990-1998, 3 folders (Box VF63)
    - [Dinner: see Nutrition] (Box VF63)
    - [Dog food: see Food--Pet foods] (Box VF63)
    - [Doughnuts: see Food--Bread] (Box VF63)
    - Eating habits, 1978-1999, 6 folders (Box VF64)
    - Eggs, 1996-2000 (Box VF64)
    - Ethnic, 1995-1998 (Box VF64)
    - Fats and oils, 1996-1999, 2 folders (Box VF64)
    - Fish, 1996-1998 (Box VF64)
    - Flavor, 1993-1998 (Box VF65)
    - Frozen, 1993-1999 (Box VF65)
    - Fruits and vegetables, 1989-1997, 2 folders (Box VF65)
    - Gourmet foods, 1989-1996 (Box VF65)
    - Health (see also Food--Industry trends), 1972-1999, Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box VF65)
    - Health (see also Food--Industry trends), 1972-1999 (continued), Folder 5 of 5 (Box VF66)
    - Home meal replacement (HMR), 1996-2000, 2 folders (Box VF66)
    - [Ice cream: see Food--Dairy--Ice Cream] (Box VF66)
    - Industry trends (see also Food--Eating habits)
      - General, 1991-1999, Folders 1-6 of 7 (Box VF66)
      - General, 1991-1999 (continued), Folder 7 of 7 (Box VF67)
      - Booklets, 1989-1995, 5 folders (Box VF67)
    - Jams/Jellies/Preserves, 1996-1998 (Box VF67)
    - [Juices: see Beverages--Juices] (Box VF67)
    - Labeling, 1994-1997 (Box VF67)
    - [Light/Weight control: see Food--Dietetic] (Box VF67)
    - [Low fat: see Food--Industry trends] (Box VF67)
    - Macaroni and Pasta, 1989-1998, 2 folders (Box VF67)
    - Margarine, 1994-1999 (Box VF67)
    - [Mayonnaise: see Food--Salad dressings and mayonnaise] (Box VF67)
    - Meat (see also Food--Poultry), 1990-1999, 3 folders (Box VF68)
    - [Milk: see Food: Dairy] (Box VF68)
    - [Mini, Miniatures: see Packaging--Mini packs] (Box VF68)
    - [Mints: see Food--Chewing gum and mints] (Box VF68)
    - [Muffins: see Food--Baked] (Box VF68)
    - [Mustard: see Food--Condiments] (Box VF68)
    - Nutraceuticals, 1995-1999 (Box VF68)
    - [Nuts: see Food--Snacks] (Box VF68)
    - [Oils: see Food--Fats and oils] (Box VF68)
    - Peanut butter, 1988-1998, 2 folders (Box VF68)
    - Pet foods (see also Pets), 1988-1998, 2 folders (Box VF68)
    - Pizza (see also Restaurants), 1996-1998 (Box VF68)
    - [Popcorn/Potato chips: see Food--Snacks] (Box VF68)
    - Poultry, 1995-1997 (Box VF68)
    - [Produce: see Food--Fruits and vegetables] (Box VF68)
    - [Salad dressings and mayonnaise: see Food--Condiments] (Box VF68)
    - [Salad/Salad bars: see Food: Fruits and vegetables] (Box VF68)
    - Salt, 1996-1998 (Box VF68)
    - Sandwiches, 1996-1998 (Box VF68)
    - Sauces, 1996-1998 (Box VF68)
    - [Shortening: see Food--Fats and oils] (Box VF68)
    - Side dishes, 1996-1998 (Box VF68)
    - Snacks
      - General, 1994-1998, Folder 1 of 5 (Box VF68)
      - General, 1994-1998 (continued), Folders 2-5 of 5 (Box VF69)
      - Popcorn, chips, etc., 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box VF69)
    - [Soft drinks: see Beverages--Soft drinks] (Box VF69)
    - Soup, 1996-1998 (Box VF69)
    - [Spaghetti: see Food--Macaroni and pasta] (Box VF69)
    - [Stuffing: see Food--Side dishes] (Box VF69)
    - Sugar, 1950-1998 (Box VF69)
    - Sugar substitutes, 1985-1998 (Box VF69)
    - Supplements: see Food--Health] (Box VF69)
    - Syrup, 1993-1996 (Box VF69)
    - [Tampering: see Tampering] (Box VF69)
    - [Taste: see Food--Flavor] (Box VF69)
    - [Tea: see Beverages--Tea] (Box VF69)
    - [Tofu: see Food--Health] (Box VF69)
    - [Unit pricing: see Prices] (Box VF69)
    - [Vegetables: see Food--Fruits and vegetables] (Box VF69)
    - Vegetarian, 1988-2000 (Box VF69)
    - [Yogurt: see Food--Dairy] (Box VF69)
  - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1967-1998 (Box VF69)
  - [Footwear: see Children's apparel/shoes; Shoes] (Box VF69)
  - [Forecasts: see Advertising--Future/Forecasts; Business--Forecasts] (Box VF69)
  - Foreign markets (see also Advertising--International)
    - General, 1996-1998 (Box VF69)
    - Africa (Box VF70)
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box VF70)
      - Zanzibar, 1962 (Box VF70)
    - Asia
      - General, 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box VF70)
      - China
        - Hong Kong, 1961-1998, 2 folders (Box VF70)
        - People's Republic, 1950s-1998, 3 folders (Box VF70)
        - Taiwan, 1981-1989 (Box VF70)
      - India, 1996-1997 (Box VF70)
      - Japan, 1983-2000 (Box VF70)
      - Singapore, 19961-1967 (Box VF70)
      - Vietnam, 1996 (Box VF70)
    - Canada, 1996-1999 (Box VF71)
    - Caribbean
      - General, 1995-1996 (Box VF71)